change to personal TikTok account but how to know if I have a personal account
company account
let's take it one step at a time
usually when we open
a TikTok account for the first time
gives us the personal account
but sometimes we get in
the finger we did not give each other
account gave us a notification and we passed each other
unintentionally on behalf of a company
for this we are going to go to the three lines of your profile
let's then go to setting and privacy
then we go to look for the account section
and when we enter it will appear
a button that says
switch to company account
this means that you are a personal account
or if it tells you to switch to personal account
this means that your account is a company
in this very simple way to make the change but
remember that there is this notification that I explain in the previous video
in case you haven't seen it because there are certain
things that company accounts need to do before
this date so this video was to tell you
how to switch to the account in the previous one I explain what is going on
with the company account
let me know in the comments if you were able to
check what type of account
you are and if this video could help you